<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>James Sann&#39;s personal website</title>
    <link>https://jamessann.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on James Sann&#39;s personal website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 12:42:03 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jamessann.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Films of 2017</title>
      <link>https://jamessann.github.io/expressions/top-5-films-of-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 12:42:03 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamessann.github.io/expressions/top-5-films-of-2017/</guid>
      <description>Top 5 Films Of 2017  Intro  5 4 3 2 1   Top 5 Films
of 2017  Honorable Mentions  The Killing a Sacred Deer The Edge of Seventeen Moonlight  Most Overrated  IT. So much praise and the kids were solid but I just didn&#39;t find Pennywise creepy enough. Dunkirk. Technically amazing but lacked any emotional connection to pull me in. Beauty and the Beast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 TV Shows of 2017</title>
      <link>https://jamessann.github.io/expressions/top-5-tv-shows-of-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 18:42:03 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamessann.github.io/expressions/top-5-tv-shows-of-2017/</guid>
      <description>Top 5 Tv Shows Of 2017  Intro  5 4 3 2 1   Top 5
Tv Shows
of 2017  Honorable Mentions  Big Little Lies — Season 1 Blue Planet II Mindhunter — Season 1 The Deuce — Season 1 Crazy Ex-Girlfriend — Season 3 SMILF — Season 1 Big Mouth — Season 1 Silicon Valley — Season 4  Most Overrated  Fargo — Season 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Albums of 2017</title>
      <link>https://jamessann.github.io/expressions/top-5-albums-of-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 14:42:03 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamessann.github.io/expressions/top-5-albums-of-2017/</guid>
      <description>Top 5 Albums Of 2017  Intro  5 4 3 2 1   Top 5 Albums
of 2017  Honorable Mentions  Woods — Love is Love Alt-J — Relaxer Mount Eerie — A Crow Looked at Me 😭 Holy Holy — Paint Julien Baker — Turn Out The Lights Spoon — Hot Thoughts Broken Social Scene — Hug of Thunder Bjork — Utopia Twin Peaks — The Return (Various Artists)  Most Overrated  You know, I can&#39;t really list anything here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 TV shows of 2016</title>
      <link>https://jamessann.github.io/expressions/top-5-tv-shows-of-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 15:28:35 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamessann.github.io/expressions/top-5-tv-shows-of-2016/</guid>
      <description>Top 5 TV Shows of 2016. Honourable Mentions  Game of Thrones — s6 Planet Earth II The Girlfriend Experience — s1 Ash vs Evil Dead — s2 Jessica Jones — s1   Most Overrated  Westworld — I stopped after three episodes because it just didn&#39;t grab my attention enough beyond the visuals. Maybe I need to pick it up again though...   Biggest Bummer  Mr Robot — s2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Albums of 2016</title>
      <link>https://jamessann.github.io/expressions/top-5-albums-of-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 14:42:03 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamessann.github.io/expressions/top-5-albums-of-2016/</guid>
      <description>Top 5 Albums of 2016 Honourable Mentions  Bat for Lashes — The Bride Radiohead — A Moon Shaped Pool Lord Huron — Lonesome Dreams Shearwater — Jet Planes and Dreams DIIV — Is the Is Are The Weeknd — Starboy Bon Iver — 22, A Million FM-84 — Atlas Stranger Things OST    Most Overrated  Radiohead — A Moon Shaped Pool. Although I really enjoyed it, the higher praise compared to their other records was 🤔.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Films of 2016</title>
      <link>https://jamessann.github.io/expressions/top-5-films-of-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 15:53:48 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamessann.github.io/expressions/top-5-films-of-2016/</guid>
      <description>5 Top Films of 2016 What a cracking year it was for cinema! Unfortunately I didn&amp;rsquo;t get the chance to see everything released in Australia in 2016 but these were the special few that stuck with me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>